<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts - Healthcare is Bullshit</title>
    <link>https://healthcareisbullshit.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Healthcare is Bullshit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>The language code for the language the website is written in</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 15:41:10 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://healthcareisbullshit.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>AMA Maintains Its Opposition to Single Ppayer System</title>
      <link>https://healthcareisbullshit.com/posts/ama-maintains-its-opposition-to-single-ppayer-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 15:41:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://healthcareisbullshit.com/posts/ama-maintains-its-opposition-to-single-ppayer-system/</guid>
      <description>AMA maintains its opposition to single-payer systems. The following are quotes from an article from Modern Health and a link to the full atricle will be include after the following excerpt
&amp;ldquo;The American Medical Association will remain opposed to proposals for the U.S. to create a single-payer healthcare system. The group voted narrowly to maintain its stance on Tuesday at its annual House of Delegates meeting.&amp;rdquo; Delegates of the largest physicians&amp;rsquo; organization voted 53% to 47% against adopting an amendment to remove the AMA&amp;rsquo;s formal opposition to a single-payer healthcare system, ending days of contentious debate that pitted the organization&amp;rsquo;s leadership against a contingent represented largely by medical students.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://healthcareisbullshit.com/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 08:48:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://healthcareisbullshit.com/posts/test/</guid>
      <description> This is a Test if you can read this you did something right. </description>
    </item><item>
      <title>The Business of Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://healthcareisbullshit.com/posts/the-business-of-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 15:42:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://healthcareisbullshit.com/posts/the-business-of-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>The Business of Health Care Depends on Exploiting Doctors and Nurses One resource seems infinite and free: the professionalism of caregivers. The following is a quote from a parent article
It is true that health care has become corporatized to an almost unrecognizable degree. But it is also true that most clinicians remain committed to the ethics that brought them into the field in the first place. This makes the hospital an inspiring place to work.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>